[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "Did he mislead or was it just a blatant lie?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "mislead", "or", "was", "it", "just", "a", "blatant", "lie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "I've had big arguments on that and friends of Obama said they're not lying.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "had", "big", "arguments", "on", "that", "and", "friends", "of", "Obama", "said", "they", "'re", "not", "lying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 28, "question": "But that wasn't lie, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "that", "was", "n't", "lie", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "In my book--", "answer_tokens": ["In", "my", "book", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "How damaging is all these to him, personally in terms of his credibility?", "question_tokens": ["How", "damaging", "is", "all", "these", "to", "him", ",", "personally", "in", "terms", "of", "his", "credibility", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBG", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "TO", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Yeah, let me say a couple of things.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "let", "me", "say", "a", "couple", "of", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "And she is the obvious head?", "question_tokens": ["And", "she", "is", "the", "obvious", "head", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Well, I believe in due course the head will roll.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "believe", "in", "due", "course", "the", "head", "will", "roll", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Do you think the fundamentally ObamaCare is a good idea, now a problem has been the implementation or you think the whole thing is basically flawed?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "fundamentally", "ObamaCare", "is", "a", "good", "idea", ",", "now", "a", "problem", "has", "been", "the", "implementation", "or", "you", "think", "the", "whole", "thing", "is", "basically", "flawed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "This is doable idea.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "doable", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "How bad is that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "bad", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "I must say I was speechless at that one.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "must", "say", "I", "was", "speechless", "at", "that", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "CC", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Can Presidents comeback in the second term when the clock is ticking from such a major fiasco?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "Presidents", "comeback", "in", "the", "second", "term", "when", "the", "clock", "is", "ticking", "from", "such", "a", "major", "fiasco", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "ERGEN: Yes, but, let me just say, I think that whether this program is going to work or not is highly problematic right now.", "answer_tokens": ["ERGEN", ":", "Yes", ",", "but", ",", "let", "me", "just", "say", ",", "I", "think", "that", "whether", "this", "program", "is", "going", "to", "work", "or", "not", "is", "highly", "problematic", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "What will?", "question_tokens": ["What", "will", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, that should worry you.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "should", "worry", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "DT", "NNP", "''", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "And how successfully can the President extricate himself from this mess?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "successfully", "can", "the", "President", "extricate", "himself", "from", "this", "mess", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "RB", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "\"THE STORY\": Well, I think it's very damaging.", "answer_tokens": ["``", "THE", "STORY", "''", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "very", "damaging", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "That's got to be pretty bad, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "got", "to", "be", "pretty", "bad", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Well, you're right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "'re", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2008"], "PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton", "Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "CD", ",", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "How does that impact on Hillary Clinton if at all?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "impact", "on", "Hillary", "Clinton", "if", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "ARANISS: Well, first of all, you're assuming that Hillary Clinton will run and she'll be the candidate, and at this point, before 2008, nobody even knew about Barack Obama.", "answer_tokens": ["ARANISS", ":", "Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "you", "'re", "assuming", "that", "Hillary", "Clinton", "will", "run", "and", "she", "'ll", "be", "the", "candidate", ",", "and", "at", "this", "point", ",", "before", "2008", ",", "nobody", "even", "knew", "about", "Barack", "Obama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Do you feel any sense of disappointment in the way this has gone?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "any", "sense", "of", "disappointment", "in", "the", "way", "this", "has", "gone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "Well, I think he said that he made a mistake.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "said", "that", "he", "made", "a", "mistake", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert Redford", "Obama"]}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "What's wrong with the country?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "wrong", "with", "the", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "But Robert Redford, was interesting about is, he came out and said that Obama's paralyzing the system, behaving stupidly.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "Robert", "Redford", ",", "was", "interesting", "about", "is", ",", "he", "came", "out", "and", "said", "that", "Obama", "'s", "paralyzing", "the", "system", ",", "behaving", "stupidly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Yeah, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton"]}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RBR", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "And then more so, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "then", "more", "so", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RBR", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "EINSTEIN: I guess there was but it was much more focused in getting Ridge (ph) good laugh and, you know, Clinton could laugh back and, you know, they joke back and forth.", "answer_tokens": ["EINSTEIN", ":", "I", "guess", "there", "was", "but", "it", "was", "much", "more", "focused", "in", "getting", "Ridge", "(", "ph", ")", "good", "laugh", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Clinton", "could", "laugh", "back", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "they", "joke", "back", "and", "forth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "At the White House last week?", "question_tokens": ["At", "the", "White", "House", "last", "week", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "At the White House.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "the", "White", "House", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Do you think that if, it was George W. Bush who made the mistake, you know, that Obama would be beating on him everyday?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "if", ",", "it", "was", "George", "W.", "Bush", "who", "made", "the", "mistake", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "Obama", "would", "be", "beating", "on", "him", "everyday", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George W. Bush", "Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "When enemies are vulnerable, you whack him, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "enemies", "are", "vulnerable", ",", "you", "whack", "him", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "I think, you know, you mean running for an election, you whack him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "mean", "running", "for", "an", "election", ",", "you", "whack", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "What was a mood like in the White House when you were there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "a", "mood", "like", "in", "the", "White", "House", "when", "you", "were", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "I think, you know, they were excited.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", ",", "you", "know", ",", "they", "were", "excited", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "``", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Can you enjoy the work of someone like Chris Christie even though he's on the other side?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "enjoy", "the", "work", "of", "someone", "like", "Chris", "Christie", "even", "though", "he", "'s", "on", "the", "other", "side", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "I love him, you know, and I think the guy is fantastic and, you know, I had a conversation with him and he said, \"Wait till I win, you know, my gubernatorial race.\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "him", ",", "you", "know", ",", "and", "I", "think", "the", "guy", "is", "fantastic", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "had", "a", "conversation", "with", "him", "and", "he", "said", ",", "``", "Wait", "till", "I", "win", ",", "you", "know", ",", "my", "gubernatorial", "race", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"], "PERSON": ["Mrs. Clinton"]}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Will you stumping to Hillary if she runs?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "stumping", "to", "Hillary", "if", "she", "runs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Anything that Mrs. Clinton asks me to do, you know, I will do because I think she represents the best path for 2016.", "answer_tokens": ["Anything", "that", "Mrs.", "Clinton", "asks", "me", "to", "do", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "will", "do", "because", "I", "think", "she", "represents", "the", "best", "path", "for", "2016", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "VBZ", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "What was it like to be behind the scenes with all this legends?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "to", "be", "behind", "the", "scenes", "with", "all", "this", "legends", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Well, one thing it was great for us to see was what it really looked like is Harvey and I were running around doing 50 other things and the cameras were capturing everything else.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "one", "thing", "it", "was", "great", "for", "us", "to", "see", "was", "what", "it", "really", "looked", "like", "is", "Harvey", "and", "I", "were", "running", "around", "doing", "50", "other", "things", "and", "the", "cameras", "were", "capturing", "everything", "else", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["million dollars", "$400,000"]}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "$", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "But in terms of money Harvey, huge amounts have been raised, more will be raised obviously from the movie as well, how is it best being used to the moment?", "question_tokens": ["But", "in", "terms", "of", "money", "Harvey", ",", "huge", "amounts", "have", "been", "raised", ",", "more", "will", "be", "raised", "obviously", "from", "the", "movie", "as", "well", ",", "how", "is", "it", "best", "being", "used", "to", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "RBR", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJS", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Robinhood eats all the overhead unlike some of the charities that we all give money to, where you find out that the charity director made a million dollars and his cousin got $400,000 and they paid for the dry cleaning, all the money.", "answer_tokens": ["Robinhood", "eats", "all", "the", "overhead", "unlike", "some", "of", "the", "charities", "that", "we", "all", "give", "money", "to", ",", "where", "you", "find", "out", "that", "the", "charity", "director", "made", "a", "million", "dollars", "and", "his", "cousin", "got", "$", "400,000", "and", "they", "paid", "for", "the", "dry", "cleaning", ",", "all", "the", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Harvey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "How many have you won now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "have", "you", "won", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "Maybe 192 Oscars.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "192", "Oscars", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Weinstein Company"], "PERSON": ["Julia Roberts", "Roberts"]}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Tell me about this movie?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "about", "this", "movie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Well, you know, at the Weinstein Company we give breaks to young, you know, talent and we decided to let Meryl Streep and Julia Roberts do this movie, you know, that Streep girl, you know, I think she's got a future and Roberts too by the way.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "at", "the", "Weinstein", "Company", "we", "give", "breaks", "to", "young", ",", "you", "know", ",", "talent", "and", "we", "decided", "to", "let", "Meryl", "Streep", "and", "Julia", "Roberts", "do", "this", "movie", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "Streep", "girl", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "she", "'s", "got", "a", "future", "and", "Roberts", "too", "by", "the", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "It's a family drama?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "family", "drama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "It's a family drama about the - this movie is a comedy believe it or not.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "family", "drama", "about", "the", "-", "this", "movie", "is", "a", "comedy", "believe", "it", "or", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Wow, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Wow", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "It's good to see you old chap.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "good", "to", "see", "you", "old", "chap", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "What the hell are you wearing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "the", "hell", "are", "you", "wearing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "These are Christian Louboutin baby.", "answer_tokens": ["These", "are", "Christian", "Louboutin", "baby", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Now you're launching the HALO Awards?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "you", "'re", "launching", "the", "HALO", "Awards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Is that supposed to be some sort of joke?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "supposed", "to", "be", "some", "sort", "of", "joke", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "No, no honestly.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "honestly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Teen Nick", "Nickelodeon"]}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "You a HALO?", "question_tokens": ["You", "a", "HALO", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Come on man it stands for helping and leading others, it's a true positive thing that we do each and every year and this is the fifth year that we're doing it with Teen Nick and Nickelodeon.", "answer_tokens": ["Come", "on", "man", "it", "stands", "for", "helping", "and", "leading", "others", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "true", "positive", "thing", "that", "we", "do", "each", "and", "every", "year", "and", "this", "is", "the", "fifth", "year", "that", "we", "'re", "doing", "it", "with", "Teen", "Nick", "and", "Nickelodeon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Right, this is the real people, young people who have done something inspiring right?", "question_tokens": ["Right", ",", "this", "is", "the", "real", "people", ",", "young", "people", "who", "have", "done", "something", "inspiring", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Yes and we take celebrities and corporations and we shine that spotlight on, you know, teenagers and their community that are making the world a better place and we connect them all together.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "and", "we", "take", "celebrities", "and", "corporations", "and", "we", "shine", "that", "spotlight", "on", ",", "you", "know", ",", "teenagers", "and", "their", "community", "that", "are", "making", "the", "world", "a", "better", "place", "and", "we", "connect", "them", "all", "together", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Because I'm not happy with it right?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "I", "'m", "not", "happy", "with", "it", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "In my country in Britain we have free healthcare right?", "question_tokens": ["In", "my", "country", "in", "Britain", "we", "have", "free", "healthcare", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Yes it works.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "it", "works", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["National Health Center"]}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Was there ever a transitional period?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "there", "ever", "a", "transitional", "period", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Obviously it was brought in the National Health Center.", "answer_tokens": ["Obviously", "it", "was", "brought", "in", "the", "National", "Health", "Center", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "At the moment, what would you say to him to try and galvanize things again for the last part of his tenure?", "question_tokens": ["At", "the", "moment", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "to", "him", "to", "try", "and", "galvanize", "things", "again", "for", "the", "last", "part", "of", "his", "tenure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "I'll say hey, haters are helping we don't argue with the help.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "say", "hey", ",", "haters", "are", "helping", "we", "do", "n't", "argue", "with", "the", "help", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "How do you feel as such a hard working American when that happens?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "as", "such", "a", "hard", "working", "American", "when", "that", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "I mean, that was unfortunate to me, I mean I felt like.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "that", "was", "unfortunate", "to", "me", ",", "I", "mean", "I", "felt", "like", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CC", "RB", "WRB", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Don't you feel sickened?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "you", "feel", "sickened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Absolutely and especially when something could come to a stalemate like that I personally was disappointed in our system but that's not the first time I've been disappointed in our system.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "and", "especially", "when", "something", "could", "come", "to", "a", "stalemate", "like", "that", "I", "personally", "was", "disappointed", "in", "our", "system", "but", "that", "'s", "not", "the", "first", "time", "I", "'ve", "been", "disappointed", "in", "our", "system", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "How do you feel about being known, particularly by me as Mr. Mariah Carey?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "being", "known", ",", "particularly", "by", "me", "as", "Mr.", "Mariah", "Carey", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "I could be called a lot worse things than that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "could", "be", "called", "a", "lot", "worse", "things", "than", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Mariah Carey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "You're waiting for your opportunity?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "waiting", "for", "your", "opportunity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Yes like a vulture.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "like", "a", "vulture", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "CC", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "What's the secret to a successful very high profile marriage?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "secret", "to", "a", "successful", "very", "high", "profile", "marriage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Not to take yourself too seriously and to actually enjoy each other, as much as you possibly can.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "to", "take", "yourself", "too", "seriously", "and", "to", "actually", "enjoy", "each", "other", ",", "as", "much", "as", "you", "possibly", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Had you ever been like properly in love before you met Mariah?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "you", "ever", "been", "like", "properly", "in", "love", "before", "you", "met", "Mariah", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "I'm a hopeless romantic so I always thought I was in love until I found the real thing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "hopeless", "romantic", "so", "I", "always", "thought", "I", "was", "in", "love", "until", "I", "found", "the", "real", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mariah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "If I said you could only be one thing for the rest of your life right?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "said", "you", "could", "only", "be", "one", "thing", "for", "the", "rest", "of", "your", "life", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "You can do TV like America's Got Talent or you can do Stand Up Comedy, which one would you do for the rest of your life?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "do", "TV", "like", "America", "'s", "Got", "Talent", "or", "you", "can", "do", "Stand", "Up", "Comedy", ",", "which", "one", "would", "you", "do", "for", "the", "rest", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "CD", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "For the rest of my life, Stand Up Comedy.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "the", "rest", "of", "my", "life", ",", "Stand", "Up", "Comedy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "That's the real soul of Nick Cannon?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "real", "soul", "of", "Nick", "Cannon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "Absolutely that's where I started, hopefully that's where I'll finish and that's -- if you see, like obviously you showed a very clean clip of the special but to get on a stage.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "that", "'s", "where", "I", "started", ",", "hopefully", "that", "'s", "where", "I", "'ll", "finish", "and", "that", "'s", "--", "if", "you", "see", ",", "like", "obviously", "you", "showed", "a", "very", "clean", "clip", "of", "the", "special", "but", "to", "get", "on", "a", "stage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "NN", ",", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Why is it called (inaudible) Nick Cannon?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "it", "called", "(", "inaudible", ")", "Nick", "Cannon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "-NONE-", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Because that's where everyone, like...", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "that", "'s", "where", "everyone", ",", "like", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Everyone says to you when they see?", "question_tokens": ["Everyone", "says", "to", "you", "when", "they", "see", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "It's unapologetic.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "unapologetic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Which side are you leaning towards?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "side", "are", "you", "leaning", "towards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "I think a little bit of both.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "both", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "You think he lied?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "he", "lied", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "I don't think he was telling the truth.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "was", "telling", "the", "truth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "It's the same thing isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "the", "same", "thing", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "Yeah, I mean that's harsh for me to say that because -- but it's you know, it's -- and I think that's where his real problem is going to be.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "mean", "that", "'s", "harsh", "for", "me", "to", "say", "that", "because", "--", "but", "it", "'s", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "--", "and", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "where", "his", "real", "problem", "is", "going", "to", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]